(Sheldon:)What are you
talking about?
(Penny:)So when do you guys think
you're gonna move in?
(Howard:)We're still figuring how much
remodeling we want to do.
(Bernadette:)It's tricky finding
the right balance
between "tasteful modern"
and "Jewish mother
tchotchke crapfest."
(Amy:)Have you made a decision
about the TARDIS?
(Amy:)I think I can sell it if we call
it, "Big British Porta-Potty."
(Howard:)We're not selling
it-- it's mine.
(Bernadette:)You can't just decide.
(Bernadette:)How about I arm-wrestle you?
(Howard:)That's not fair.
(Howard:)It's like me challenging you
to a sexy pants contest.
(Raj:)You could play
Ping-Pong for it.
(Howard:)I would do that.
(Bernadette:)How is that fair?
(Bernadette:)You grew up
with a table.
(Howard:)Yes, but I mostly used it
as a battlefield
(Howard:)in an ongoing war between the
Transformers and the ThunderCats
(Howard:)for control of a bra
I had found in the woods.